Columbia Pictures stills and key books LSC.2213
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 1. Large files
  - TANK FORCE (folder listed as NO TIME TO DIE), (1958) (Box 104)
  - TARAWA BEACHHEAD, (1958) (Box 92)
  - TAXI DRIVER, (1976) (Box 460)
  - TAXI DRIVER, (1975) (Box 460)
  - TAXI DRIVER, (1975) (Box 460)
  - TEENAGE STORY (released as LIFE BEGINS AT 17), (1958) (Box 64)
  - TENDER IS THE NIGHT, (1962) (Box 165)
  - TENDER IS THE NIGHT, (1962) (Box 167)
  - TEXICAN, THE, (1966) (Box 130)
  - TEXICAN, THE, (1966) (Box 221)
  - THANK YOU ALL VERY MUCH (folder titled THANK YOU VERY MUCH), (1969) (Box 107)
  - THANK YOU ALL VERY MUCH (folder titled THANK YOU VERY MUCH), (1969) (Box 380)
  - THANK YOU ALL VERY MUCH (folder titled THANK YOU VERY MUCH), (1969) (Box 553)
  - THAT MAN IN ISTANBUL, (1965) (Box 131)
  - THAT MAN IN ISTANBUL, (1965) (Box 220)
  - THE FINAL CONFLICT, (1981) (Box 558)
  - THERE'S A GIRL IN MY SOUP, (1970) (Box 84)
  - THERE'S A GIRL IN MY SOUP, (1970) (Box 380)
  - THERE'S A GIRL IN MY SOUP, (1970) (Box 550)
  - THESE ARE THE DAMNED, (1963) (Box 66)
  - THESE ARE THE DAMNED, (1963) (Box 212)
  - THESE ARE THE DAMNED, (1963) (Box 536)
  - THESE THOUSAND HILLS, (1959) (Box 27)
  - THESE THOUSAND HILLS, (1959) (Box 31)
  - THINGS OF LIFE, THE (US release title), (1970) (Box 52)
  - THINGS OF LIFE, THE (US release title), (1970) (Box 336)
  - THINGS OF LIFE, THE (US release title), (1970) (Box 547)
  - THIRD VOICE, THE, (1960) (Box 116)
  - THIS BITTER EARTH (released as THIS ANGRY AGE), (1958) (Box 28)
  - THREE ON A COUCH, (1966) (Box 3)
  - THREE ON A COUCH, (1966) (Box 385)
  - THREE ON A COUCH, (1966) (Box 521)
  - THREE ON A COUCH, (1966) (Box 522)
  - THREE STOOGES GO AROUND THE WORLD IN A DAZE, THE, (1963) (Box 95)
  - THREE STOOGES GO AROUND THE WORLD IN A DAZE, THE, (1963) (Box 436)
  - THREE STOOGES IN ORBIT, THE, (1962) (Box 113)
  - THREE STOOGES IN ORBIT, THE, (1962) (Box 437)
  - THREE STOOGES MEET HERCULES, THE, (1962) (Box 437)
  - TIGER MAKES OUT, THE, (1967) (Box 112)
  - TIGER MAKES OUT, THE, (1967) (Box 375)
  - TIJUANA STORY, THE, (1957) (Box 53)
  - TIME FOR KILLING, A, (1967) (Box 112)
  - TIME FOR KILLING, A, (1967) (Box 288)
  - TIME FOR KILLING, A, (1967) (Box 291)
  - TIME FOR KILLING, A, (1967) (Box 292)
  - TINGLER, THE, (1959) (Box 112)
  - TINGLER, THE, (1959) (Box 432)
  - TO SIR, WITH LOVE, (1967) (Box 110)
  - TO SIR, WITH LOVE, (1967) (Box 380)
  - TORTURE GARDEN, THE, (1967) (Box 76)
  - TORTURE GARDEN, THE, (1967) (Box 415)
  - TORTURE GARDEN, THE, (1967) (Box 518)
  - TOUCHABLES, THE, (1968) (Box 164)
  - TOUCHABLES, THE, (1968) (Box 167)
  - TRAITOR'S GATE, (1964) (Box 256)
  - TRIAL OF CAPTAIN BARRETT (released as THE WORLD WAS HIS JURY), (1958) (Box 75)
  - TROUBLE WITH ANGELS, THE, (1966) (Box 69)
  - TROUBLE WITH ANGELS, THE, (1966) (Box 330)
  - TROUBLE WITH ANGELS, THE, (1966) (Box 426)
  - TROUBLE WITH ANGELS, THE, (1966) (Box 427)
  - TWIST AROUND THE CLOCK, (1961) (Box 48)
  - TWIST AROUND THE CLOCK, (1961) (Box 277)
  - TWO-HEADED SPY, (1958) (Box 180)
  - TWO-HEADED SPY (folder titled THE CLOCK WITHOUT A FACE), (1958) (Box 58)
  - UNDER THE YUM YUM TREE, (1963) (Box 81)
  - UNDER THE YUM YUM TREE, (1963) (Box 148)
  - UNDER THE YUM YUM TREE, (1963) (Box 299)
  - UNDER THE YUM YUM TREE, (1963) (Box 300)
  - UNDERWATER CITY, THE, (1962) (Box 95)
  - UNDERWATER CITY, THE, (1962) (Box 344)
  - UNDERWORLD, U.S.A., (1961) (Box 63)
  - UNDERWORLD, U.S.A., (1961) (Box 262)
  - UPSTAIRS AND DOWNSTAIRS, (1959) (Box 23)
  - VALACHI PAPERS, THE, (1972) (Box 13)
  - VALACHI PAPERS, THE, (1972) (Box 551)
  - VALACHI PAPERS, THE, (1972) (Box 552)
  - VALLEY OF THE DRAGONS, (1961) (Box 75)
  - VALLEY OF THE DRAGONS, (1961) (Box 270)
  - VALLEY OF THE REDWOODS, (1960) (Box 35)
  - VICTORS, THE, (1963) (Box 148)
  - VICTORS, THE, (1963) (Box 273)
  - VICTORS, THE, (1963) (Box 274)
  - VICTORS, THE, (1963) (Box 275)
  - VIRGIN SOLDIERS, THE, (1969) (Box 107)
  - VIRGIN SOLDIERS, THE, (1969) (Box 380)
  - VIRGIN SOLDIERS, THE, (1969) (Box 543)
  - VISA TO CANTON, (1961) (Box 47)
  - VON-RYAN'S EXPRESS, (1965) (Box 35)
  - WACKIEST SHIP IN THE ARMY, THE, (1960) (Box 127)
  - WACKIEST SHIP IN THE ARMY, THE, (1960) (Box 326)
  - WAKE ME WHEN IT'S OVER, (1960) (Box 165)
  - WALK DON'T RUN, (1966) (Box 134)
  - WALK DON'T RUN, (1966) (Box 280)
  - WALK DON'T RUN, (1966) (Box 281)
  - WALK IN THE SPRING RAIN, A, (1970) (Box 7)
  - WALK IN THE SPRING RAIN, A, (1970) (Box 381)
  - WALK IN THE SPRING RAIN, A, (1970) (Box 550)
  - WALK ON THE WILD SIDE, (1962) (Box 76)
  - WALK ON THE WILD SIDE, (1962) (Box 275)
  - WALK THE LINE, I, (1970) (Box 130)
  - WALK THE LINE, I, (1970) (Box 355)
  - WALK WITH LOVE AND DEATH, A, (1969) (Box 272)
  - WAR LOVER, THE, (1962) (Box 12)
  - WAR LOVER, THE, (1962) (Box 276)
  - WATCH IT, SAILOR, (1961) (Box 132)
  - WATERMELON MAN, THE, (1970) (Box 105)
  - WATERMELON MAN, THE, (1970) (Box 381)
  - WATERMELON MAN, THE, (1970) (Box 543)
  - WATTSTAX, (1973) (Box 103)
  - WATTSTAX, (1973) (Box 382)
  - WATTSTAX, (1973) (Box 545)
  - WAY WE WERE, THE, (1973) (Box 382)
  - WAY WE WERE, THE, (1973) (Box 382)
  - WAY WE WERE, THE, (1973) (Box 383)
  - WAY WE WERE, THE, (1973) (Box 488)
  - WAY WE WERE, THE, (1973) (Box 489)
  - WAY WE WERE, THE, (1973) (Box 546)
  - WAY... WAY OUT, (1966) (Box 33)
  - WELCOME TO THE CLUB, (1971) (Box 59)
  - WELCOME TO THE CLUB, (1971) (Box 383)
  - WELCOME TO THE CLUB, (1971) (Box 544)
  - WE'LL BURY YOU, (1971) (Box 383)
  - WHERE ANGELS GO... TROUBLE FOLLOWS, (1968) (Box 110)
  - WHERE ANGELS GO... TROUBLE FOLLOWS, (1968) (Box 148)
  - WHERE ANGELS GO... TROUBLE FOLLOWS, (1968) (Box 307)
  - WHERE ANGELS GO... TROUBLE FOLLOWS, (1968) (Box 308)
  - WHERE ANGELS GO... TROUBLE FOLLOWS, (1968) (Box 309)
  - WHERE ANGELS GO... TROUBLE FOLLOWS, (1968) (Box 310)
  - WHERE ANGELS GO... TROUBLE FOLLOWS, (1968) (Box 311)
  - WHITE SISTER [aka BIANCO, ROSSE E...], (1972) (Box 62)
  - WHITE SISTER [aka BIANCO, ROSSE E...], (1972) (Box 466)
  - WHO WAS THAT LADY?, (1960) (Box 289)
  - WHO WAS THAT LADY?, (1960) (Box 290)
  - WHO WAS THAT LADY?, (1960) (Box 123)
  - WHO'S MINDING THE MINT?, (1967) (Box 126)
  - WHO'S MINDING THE MINT?, (1967) (Box 296)
  - WHO'S MINDING THE MINT?, (1967) (Box 297)
  - WHY AMERICA? (US release title), (1969) (Box 61)
  - WHY AMERICA? (US release title), (1969) (Box 375)
  - WHY AMERICA? (US release title), (1969) (Box 545)
  - WILD RIVER, (1960) (Box 166)
  - WILD WESTERNERS, (1962) (Box 286)
  - WILD WESTERNERS, THE, (1962) (Box 130)
  - WIND CANNOT READ, THE, (1958) (Box 39)
  - WINTER A GO-GO, (1965) (Box 91)
  - WINTER A-GO-GO, (1965) (Box 287)
  - WITHOUT A TRACE, (1983) (Box 491)
  - WOMAN HUNT, (1962) (Box 123)
  - WOMAN OBSESSED, (1959) (Box 123)
  - WOMAN OBSESSED, (1959) (Box 147)
  - WORLD OF TOPO GIGIO, (1965) (Box 217)
  - WORLD WITHOUT SUN (US release title), (1964) (Box 109)
  - WRECKING CREW, THE, (1969) (Box 439)
  - WRECKING CREW, THE, (1969) (Box 440)
  - WRECKING CREW, THE, (1969) (Box 441)
  - WRONG BOX, THE, (1966) (Box 126)
  - WRONG BOX, THE, (1966) (Box 175)
  - X, Y & ZEE (release title X Y & Z), (1972) (Box 40)
  - X, Y & ZEE (release title X Y & Z), (1972) (Box 367)
  - X, Y & ZEE (release title X Y & Z), (1972) (Box 544)
  - YESTERDAY'S ENEMY, (1959) (Box 71)
  - YESTERDAY'S ENEMY, (1959) (Box 305)
  - YOU CAN'T WIN 'EM ALL, (1970) (Box 15)
  - YOU CAN'T WIN 'EM ALL, (1970) (Box 345)
  - YOU CAN'T WIN 'EM ALL, (1970) (Box 546)
  - YOU MUST BE JOKING, (1965) (Box 96)
  - YOU MUST BE JOKING, (1965) (Box 436)
  - YOUNG AMERICANS, THE, (1967) (Box 111)
  - YOUNG AMERICANS, THE, (1967) (Box 388)
  - YOUNG AMERICANS, THE, (1967) (Box 514)
  - YOUNG AMERICANS, THE, (1967) (Box 515)
  - YOUNG FRANKENSTEIN, (1974) (Box 563)
  - YOUNG WINSTON, (1972) (Box 59)
  - YOUNG WINSTON, (1972) (Box 350)
  - YOUNG WINSTON, (1972) (Box 547)
  - YOUNG WINSTON, (1972) (Box 555)
  - ZOTZ!, (1962) (Box 105)
  - ZOTZ!, (1962) (Box 219)
  - ZOTZ!, (1962) (Box 220)
- Series 2. Small files
  Files in this series typically each contain fewer than thirty images.
  - ASSIGNMENT: PARIS, (1952) (Box 579, Folder 1)
  - ALL ASHORE, (1953) (Box 579, Folder 2)
  - BLONDIE, (1938) (Box 579, Folder 3)
  - ARIZONA (Box 579, Folder 4)
  - THE BRAVE BULLS, (1951) (Box 579, Folder 5)
  - THE BLACK KNIGHT, (1954) (Box 579, Folder 6)
  - BLUE CANADIAN ROCKIES, (1952) (Box 579, Folder 7)
  - Bowman, Lee, undated (Box 579, Folder 8)
  - Young, Loretta, undated (Box 579, Folder 9)
  - BRAVE WARRIOR, i1952) (Box 579, Folder 10)
  - THE BRIGAND, (1952) (Box 579, Folder 11)
  - THE CAINE MUTINY, (1954) (Box 579, Folder 12)
  - The Columbia bowling team, (undated) (Box 579, Folder 13)
  - CAPTAIN BLOOD: FUGITIVE (aka CAPTAIN PIRATE), (1952) (Box 579, Folder 14)
  - COMBAT SQUAD, (1952) (Box 579, Folder 15)
  - Borg, Veda Ann, )undated) (Box 579, Folder 16)
  - CRUISIN' DOWN THE RIVER, (1953) (Box 579, Folder 17)
  - Carter, Janis, (undated) (Box 579, Folder 18)
  - Duryea, Dan, (undated) (Box 579, Folder 19)
  - EL ALAMEIN, (1953) (Box 579, Folder 20)
  - DRIVE A CROOKED ROAD, (1954) (Box 579, Folders 21-22)
  - THE NEBRASKAN, (1953) (Box 579, Folder 23)
  - EVERYTHING'S DUCKY, (1961) (Box 579, Folder 24)
  - BELL, BOOK, AND CANDLE, (1958) (Box 579, Folder 25)
  - OVER-EXPOSED, (1956) (Box 579, Folder 26)
  - THE PETTY GIRL, (1950) (Box 579, Folder 27)
  - Palmer, Betsy, (undated) (Box 579, Folder 28)
  - Peters, Susan, (circa 1948) (Box 579, Folder 29)
  - Parks, Larry et al, (undated) (Box 579, Folder 30)
  - World War II publicity, (undated) (Box 579, Folder 31)
  - Reason, Rex, (undated) (Box 579, Folder 32)
  - Randall, Norma, (undated) (Box 579, Folder 33)
  - Ross, Lois, (undated) (Box 579, Folder 34)
  - Sutton, Grady and Frank Ryan, (undated) (Box 579, Folder 35)
  - RIGHT GUY (released as GOOD LUCK, MR. YATES), (1943) (Box 579, Folder 36)
  - Miscellaneous negatives, (undated) (Box 579, Folder 37)
    Includes Humphrey Bogart, John Wayne, Vincent Price.
  - Ralph, Jessie, (undated) (Box 579, Folder 38)
  - Sullivan, Ed, (undated) (Box 579, Folder 39)
  - THE SARACEN BLADE, 1954 (Box 579, Folder 40)
  - Stanwyck, Barbara, (undated) (Box 579, Folder 41)
  - SABRE AND THE ARROW (aka LAST OF THE COMANCHES), (1953) (Box 579, Folder 42)
  - SAILOR'S HOLIDAY, (1944) (Box 579, Folder 43)
  - Stewart, Jimmy with Dwight Eisenhower[?], (undated) (Box 579, Folder 44)
  - SALOME, (1953) (Box 579, Folder 45)
  - START CHEERING, (1938) (Box 579, Folder 46)
  - THE SHADOW ON THE WINDOW, (1957) (Box 579, Folder 47)
  - TIME OUT FOR RHYTHM, (1941) (Box 579, Folder 48)
  - Totter, Audrey, (undated) (Box 579, Folder 49)
  - TRIPLE THREAT, (1948) (Box 579, Folder 50)
  - Towers, Constance, (undated) (Box 579, Folder 51)
  - UNDERCOVER MAN, (1949) (Box 579, Folder 52)
  - Vidor, Charles, (undated) (Box 579, Folder 53)
  - THE WALLS CAME TUMBLING DOWN, (1946) (Box 579, Folder 54)
  - Windsor, Georgette, (undated) (Box 579, Folder 55)
  - Young, Loretta, (undated) (Box 579, Folder 56)
  - Fashion portraits, (circa 1942) (Box 579, Folder 57)
    Includes Leslie Brooks.
  - Fashion - general publicity, (undated) (Box 579, Folder 58)
    Includes Pat Parrish.
  - FORT TI, (1953) (Box 579, Folder 59)
  - FOOTSTEPS IN THE FOG, (1955) (Box 579, Folder 60)
  - Ford. Glenn, (undated) (Box 579, Folder 61)
  - Fellows Edith, (undated) (Box 579, Folder 62)
  - Flowerton, Consuelo, (undated) (Box 579, Folder 63)
  - Kerr, Deborah, (undated) (Box 579, Folder 64)
  - THE GARMENT JUNGLE, (1957) (Box 579, Folder 65)
  - GENE AUTRY AND THE MOUNTIES, (1951) (Box 579, Folder 66)
  - HARRIET CRAIG, (1950) (Box 579, Folder 67)
  - THE HAPPY TIME, (1952) (Box 579, Folder 68)
  - Holliday, Judy / THE MARRYING KIND, (1952) (Box 579, Folder 69)
  - HARMON OF MICHIGAN, (1941) (Box 579, Folder 70)
  - KILL THE UMPIRE, (1950) (Box 579, Folder 71)
  - Henry, Gloria, (undated) (Box 579, Folder 72)
  - HIGHLY IRREGULAR (aka THE WIFE TAKES A FLYER), (1942) (Box 579, Folder 73)
  - Kalloch, Robert, (undated) (Box 579, Folder 74)
  - Laine, Frankie, (undated) (Box 579, Folder 75)
  - LUST FOR GOLD, (1949) (Box 579, Folder 76)
  - MacMurray, Fred, (undated) (Box 579, Folder 77)
  - MY SIX CONVICTS, (1952) (Box 579, Folder 78)
  - Merrick, Lynn, (undated) (Box 579, Folder 79)
  - MISSION OVER KOREA, (1953) (Box 579, Folder 80)
  - THE MAD MAGICIAN, (1954) (Box 579, Folder 81)
  - Medina, Patricia, (undated) (Box 579, Folder 82)
  - Martin, Tony, (undated) (Box 579, Folder 83)
  - MISS GRANT TAKES RICHMOND, (1949) (Box 579, Folder 84)
  - Menjou, Adolphe, (undated) (Box 579, Folder 85)
  - MY SISTER EILEEN, (1955) (Box 579, Folder 86)
  - THE LONG GRAY LINE, (1955) (Box 579, Folder 87)
  - GALLANT JOURNEY, (1946) (Box 579, Folders 88-91)
  - Charlita / THE BRAVE BULLS, (1951) (Box 580, Folder 1)
  - Bellamy, Ralph, (undated); Badly faded. (Box 580, Folder 2)
  - Borg, Veda Ann, (undated) (Box 580, Folder 3)
  - BLUE CANADIAN ROCKIES, (1952) (Box 580, Folder 4)
  - Bowman, Lee, (undated) (Box 580, Folder 5)
  - Young, Loretta, (undated) (Box 580, Folder 6)
    Portraits by George Hurrell.
  - Bartlett, Michael, (1935); Badly faded. (Box 580, Folder 7)
  - Burgess, Dorothy, (1934); Badly faded. (Box 580, Folder 8)
  - Byron, Walter, (undated) (Box 580, Folder 9)
  - Blakely, James, (undated); Badly faded. (Box 580, Folder 10)
  - Bond, Lilian, (1934); Badly faded. (Box 580, Folder 11)
  - Buckler, John, (1934); Most of the photos are badly faded. (Box 580, Folder 12)
  - BRAVE WARRIOR, (1952) (Box 580, Folder 13)
    Photographs by Robert Coburn.
  - THE BRIGAND, (1952) (Box 580, Folder 14)
    Photographs by Edward Cronenweth.
  - Britton, Mozelle, (undated) (Box 580, Folder 15)
  - THE CAINE MUTINY, (1953) (Box 580, Folder 16)
    Stills by Irving Lippman.
  - Birch, Wyrley, (1935); Badly faded. (Box 580, Folder 17)
  - Columbia bowling team, (undated) (Box 580, Folder 18)
  - Allen, Robert and Evelyn Pierce, (1934); Badly faded. (Box 580, Folder 19)
  - CAPTAIN BLOOD, FUGITIVE (aka CAPTAIN PIRATE), (1952) (Box 580, Folder 20)
  - Carlisle, Mary, (1934); Badly faded. (Box 580, Folder 21)
  - Colbert, Claudette, (1935); Most of the photographs are badly faded. (Box 580, Folder 22)
    Photographs by Ray Jones.
  - CRUISIN' DOWN THE RIVER, (1953) (Box 580, Folder 23)
    Stills by Irving Lippmann; portraits of Bily Daniels by Robert Coburn.
  - Cook, Donald, (1934); Badly faded. (Box 580, Folder 24)
    Also includes stills fom A MIDSUMMER NIGHT'S DREAM (Warner Bros., 1935).
  - Dale, Virginia, (1934); Badly faded. (Box 580, Folder 25)
  - Carroll, Nancy / I'LL LOVE YOU ALWAYS, (1935); Most photos are badly faded. (Box 580, Folders 26-27)
    Some photos by A. L. Schafer and Irving Lippmann.
  - Duryea, Dan, (undated) (Box 580, Folder 28)
    Portraits by Edward Cronenweth.
  - Courtney, Inez, (1934-1935); Badly faded. (Box 580, Folder 29)
  - DRIVE A CROOKED ROAD, (1954) (Box 580, Folder 30)
    Portraits of Mickey Rooney by Irving Lippmann.
  - THE NEBRASKAN, (1953) (Box 580, Folder 31)
    Portraits of Philip Carey by Edward Cronenweth.
  - EVERYTHING'S DUCKY, (1961) (Box 580, Folder 32)
    Portraits of Elizabeth MacRae by Jack Gereghty.
  - Fashion photos, (undated) (Box 580, Folder 33)
    Includes: K. T. Stevens; Pat Parrish.
  - Fashion photos, (1934); Badly faded. (Box 580, Folders 34-35)
  - O'Neil, Sally, (undated) (Box 580, Folder 36)
    Portrait by Ray Jones.
  - Patrick, Gail, (1934); Badly faded. (Box 580, Folder 37)
  - Page, Bradley, (undated) (Box 580, Folder 38)
  - Peters, Susan and Robert Cummings, (1949) (Box 580, Folder 38)
    Photos by Irving Lippmann.
  - Perry, Joan, (1935); Badly faded. (Box 580, Folder 39)
  - SHE'S A SWEETHEART, (1944) (Box 580, Folder 40)
  - Pepper, Barbara, (circa 1938) (Box 580, Folder 41)
  - STORM OVER TIBET, (1952) (Box 580, Folder 42)
  - Robson, May, (circa 1933); Many photos are badly faded. (Box 580, Folder 43)
  - Randall, Norma, (undated) (Box 580, Folder 44)
    Portraits by Edard Cronenweth.
  - Raymond, Gene, (circa 1935); Most photos are badly faded. (Box 580, Folders 45-47)
  - Revier, Dorothy, (undated) (Box 580, Folder 48)
  - Miscellaneous prints, (1935-circa 1943) (Box 580, Folder 49)
    Includes: Edward G. Robinson; Ann Miller in World War II propaganda.
  - Read, Barbara, (circa 1935) (Box 580, Folder 50)
  - Arrowhead trip, (1934); Badly faded. (Box 580, Folder 51)
  - Schildkraut, Joseph, (circa 1935); Most photos are badly faded. (Box 580, Folder 52)
  - Del Monte trip, (1934); Most photos are badly faded. (Box 580, Folder 53)
  - Stanwyck, Barbara, (undated) (Box 580, Folder 54)
  - THE SABRE AND THE ARROW (aka LAST OF THE COMANCHES), (1953) (Box 580, Folder 55)
  - THE SHADOW ON THE WINDOW, (1957) (Box 580, Folder 56)
    Portraits by Edward Cronenweth; off-camera photos by Roobert Coburn.
  - Miscellaneous portraits, (1934); Badly faded. (Box 580, Folder 57)
  - SAILOR'S HOLIDAY, (1944) (Box 508, Folder 58)
    Cast portrait by Joe Walters.
  - START CHEERING, (1938) (Box 580, Folder 59)
  - Miscellaneous publicity photos, (1934); Badly faded. (Box 580, Folders 60-62)
  - Towers, Constance, (1933) (Box 580, Folder 63)
    Baby pictures.
  - Vidor, Charles, (undated) (Box 580, Folder 64)
    Portrait by Al St. Hilaire.
  - THE WALLS CAME TUMBLING DOWN, (1946) (Box 580, Folder 65)
  - Windsor, Georgette, (undated) (Box 580, Folder 66)
  - Wyatt, Jane (Box 580, Folder 67)
  - Young, Loretta, (undated) (Box 580, Folder 68)
  - Seward, Billie, (1935); Most photos are badly faded. (Box 580, Folders 69-73)
  - FOOTSTEPS IN THE FOG, (1955) (Box 580, Folder 74)
    Portraits of Jean Simmons by Robert Coburn.
  - THE RETURN OF OCTOBER, (1948) (Box 580, Folder 75)
  - Fellows, Edith, (circa 1936) (Box 580, Folders 76-77)
  - Flowerton, Consuelo, (undated) (Box 580, Folder 78)
  - THE GARMENT JUNGLE, 1957 (Box 580, Folder 79)
    Portraits of Gia Scala by Robert Coburn.
  - HARRIET CRAIG, (1950) (Box 580, Folder 80)
  - GENE AUTRY AND THE MOUNTIES, (1951) (Box 580, Folder 81)
  - THE HAPPY TIME, (1952) (Box 580, Folder 82)
  - Hohl, Arthur, (1935); Badly faded. (Box 580, Folder 83)
  - THE MARRYING KIND, (1952) (Box 580, Folder 84)
    Portraits of Judy Holliday by Edward Cronenweth.
  - KILL THE UMPIRE, (1950) (Box 580, Folder 85)
  - Harvey, Lilian, (1934); Badly faded. (Box 580, Folder 86)
  - Jory, Victor, (1935); Badly faded. (Box 580, Folder 87)
  - Kalloch, Robert, (circa 1935); Most photos are badly faded. (Box 580, Folder 88)
  - Laine, Frankie, (undated) (Box 580, Folder 89)
  - Lindsay, Lois, (1935); Badly faded. (Box 580, Folder 90)
  - Marsh, Marian, (1934-1935); Some photos badly faded. (Box 580, Folder 91)
  - MY SIX CONVICTS, (1952) (Box 580, Folder 92)
  - MISSION OVER KOREA, (1953) (Box 580, Folder 93)
  - Middlemass, Robert, (1935); Badly faded. (Box 580, Folder 94)
  - Michaels, Beverly, (undated) (Box 580, Folder 95)
  - MR. WINKLE GOES TO WAR, (1944) (Box 580, Folder 96)
  - THE MAD MAGICIAN, (1954) (Box 580, Folder 97)
  - Medina, Patricia, (undated) (Box 580, Folder 98)
  - Palm Springs trip / George Murphy, (1934); Badly faded. (Box 580, Folder 99)
  - Moore, Grace, (1935); Badly faded. (Box 580, Folder 100)
  - MY SISTER EILEEN, (1955) (Box 580, Folder 101)
    Janet Leigh practicing ballet.
  - THE LONG GRAY LINE, (1955) (Box 580, Folder 102)
  - GALLANT JOURNEY, (1946) (Box 580, Folder 103)